konkanrailway.com 2019-06-10

# Konkan Railway

  1. [Home](http://www.konkanrailway.com/ "Home")
  2. Mobile App Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Is built for KRCL Mobile Apps as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by, at no cost and is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform Mobile application users regarding KRCL policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use KRCL Service.

If you choose to use KRCL Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that KRCL will collect is used for providing and improving the Service. KRCL will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

For a better experience, while using KRCL  Service, KRCL may require you to provide   certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to Name, Email Address, Mobile number, Date of Birth.

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app

**Security**

KRCL values your trust in providing your Personal Information, and will use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. However KRCL cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

KRCL may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. KRCL will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes will be effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact KRCL.
